{
    "id": "6959cae410714014810bbb321a1d934e",
    "title": "About, Off, On And Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Did you hear …………….. the explosion at the mall?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "619e89c477874e9bba992caa32fe437e"
        },
        {
            "question": "That song reminds me …………………. my childhood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ff738786afe49e2a3a570d1e91d099d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She complained ………………….. his rude behavior.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "off",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ab4ad4204bd4c89a1193c5ac3849e95"
        },
        {
            "question": "They took him to hospital when he complained …………………. chest pain and uneasiness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a3eb1625cd354dafaa788a57e6b54f94"
        },
        {
            "question": "He warned me ……………….. dire consequences.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db0e99568aa3485fb79be9f0801d64aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you heard …………………. him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5c9b51dfb4834c96a1817bc4fb5c11a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did you think ………………… his latest film?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c147c7a5459a448a9098c2edf83ed099"
        },
        {
            "question": "We haven’t decided but we are thinking ……………….. moving to a bigger home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "77021672baaf4448be9fc621bbb6d9b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wouldn’t dream …………………. doing something like that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "77ded95638f54c8cb4eb281b92b66394"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had never thought ………………… it before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d6f5a82ff52646d392fc310f6c6e29da"
        }
    ]
}